# **BRAVARD** Amadis

amadis.bravard[AT]outlook.com - https://www.amadisbravard.fr/ A https://www.linkedin.com/in/dix/ - 🌀 https://www.github.com/dix/

French/English - 💓 Lille, France

# Technical Lead/Solution Architect

For more than ten years, first as a Full-Stack Software Engineer then as a Technical Lead, I was able to learn about various functional domains (healthcare, banking/insurance...) while working with multiple technologies (Java, Angular, Node.js, Unix, Cloud...).

Now, after collecting and analyzing the requirements, I design interoperability solutions that best meet the expectations of customers/users while staying within the constraints of each stakeholder.

If it isn't documented, it doesn't exist

# Professional Experience

## 2019-01 to Present: Dedalus (ex-Inovelan) - Healthcare

#### 2020-06 to Present: Solution Architect

- Collecting and analyzing the requirements
- Designing solutions with the international partners
- Tracking their implementation
- Making and documenting technical POC

#### **Environment**

- J2EE, Spring, Node.js, REST, HL7 FHIR, Keycloak, Apache Pulsar, Prometheus, Grafana, Docker, Unix, WSL 2
- 5 to 20 people

#### 2019-01 to Present: Technical Lead

- Implementing development industrialization practices (ticketing, documentation, process, code review...)
- Organizing brainstorms and continuous improvement practice workshops (technical, English...)
- Participating in presales, technical and functional designing workshops
- Participating in developments
- Conducting technical interviews

#### **Environment**

- J2EE, Angular, Wildfly, Drone Cl, Jira, Confluence, Visual Studio Code, Agile (Scrum), Git (Gitea)
- 5 to 20 people

# 2010-11 to 2018-12 : GFI Informatique - IT Services

### 2016-06 to 2018-12: Technical Lead - Pacifica (Crédit Agricole) - Insurance

- Training and monitoring the team members
- Backup project manager
- Estimating, designing and implementing features/fixes Writing technical and functional documentation
- Conducting technical interviews

- J2EE, AngularJS, Angular, TypeScript, RxJS, Quality Center, IntelliJ, WebStorm, Agile (Scrum), Git (GitLab)
- 5 to 20 people

## 2015-11 to 2016-05: Technical Analyst - Metro Cash&Carry - Retail

Designing and developing features/fixes

#### **Environment**

- PL/SQL, Bash, Java, ClearCase
- 5 people

#### 2014-06 to 2015-11: Technical Analyst - Payline (Monext) - Web payment

- Designing and developing features/fixes
- Connecting with partners API (PayPal, SEPA, Paylib, Skrill...) Quality control : PCI DSS/OWASP Top 10
- Managing development/testing environments
- Training the team members

#### Environment

- J2EE, Hibernate, Soap, REST, MySQL, Bash, Jenkins, Jira, Unix, CVS, Git (GitLab)
- 5 to 20 people

# 2012-04 to 2012-06: Technical Analyst - France Télécom (Orange) - Automation

- Collecting and analyzing requirements of the team members
- Developing tasks automation scripts: app synchronization, development environment setup, server management

#### **Environment**

- J2EE, Spring, Visual Basic, Bash, Selenium, Jahia, Apache Tomcat, Unix, SVN
- 15 people

# 2011-01 to 2012-04 then 2012-06 to 2014-06: Technical Analyst - Pacifica (Crédit Agricole) - Insurance

- Estimating, designing and developing features/fixes
- Training and monitoring the team members
- Writing technical and functional documentation

#### **Environment**

- J2EE, JavaScript, jQuery, Apache Tomcat, Mantis, Quality Center, Eclipse, SVN
- 5 to 20 people

#### 2010-11 to 2011-01: Internship

Developing features/fixes on an internal time-tracking app

#### **Environment**

- J2EE, Spring, GWT, Eclipse, SVN
- 3 people

# Education/Training

### **Professionals**

2016-12 : Développement d'applications riches avec Angular 2 - Zénika 2016-05 : AngularJS, maîtriser le Framework JavaScript de Google – Orsys

2015-04 : OWASP, Sécurité des Applications - Advens

2009-01 to 2011-01: D.U.T. Informatique - IUT A Lille 1



Some Cycling (utility, road, virtual & MTB)

Personal Knowledge Management

Soap-making